(Bernadette:)Isn't that right, Raj?
(Raj:)Uh, yeah, I mean,
her serve was pretty good.
(Bernadette:)Come on, get
in her head.
(Bernadette:)Be intimidating.
(Raj:)Okay, uh...
I'm gonna own you, bitch!
Whoa!
Hey!
(Amy:)That's not nice.
(Raj:)Let's just play.
(Howard:)One-zero.
WOLOWITZ:
Two.
(Raj:)Three.
(Leonard:)Four.
(Howard:)Five-nothing.
(chuckles)
Wait,
(Howard:)did you play badminton
(Howard:)or sad-minton?
(Leonard:)Don't listen to him--
all she's got is a serve.
(Bernadette:)Now, grab a fresh tampon
and put her away.
Wha...?
A-And that's not offensive?
(Raj:)Where's the line?
(Penny:)It's in your purse. Play.
BERNADETTE:
One-five.
(Bernadette:)Two-five.
(Bernadette:)Three-five.
(Bernadette:)Four-five.
Five-five!